Guide to the Frances Logan Merriam papers 1948-1972
Montana Historical Society
- Committee For Paradise Dam
  - Hearings
    - Knowles Dam hearing (includes testimony of Frances D. Logan; Gus Norwood; Arnold Olsen; Kenneth Holum, Assistant Secretary of Interior; Ralph Maxwell, Lake County Commissioners; J.E. Corette, Montana Power Company; George E. Mushbach; John W. Haw and Carl H. Burgess, Northern Pacific Railway Company; Mark Hatfield; Robert C. Sykes, Montana Wildlife Federation; Walter H. Morigeau, Confederated Salish and Kootenai Tribes; Ray M. Logan, Upper Columbia Development Council; J. Hugo Aronson), 1962 (Box-folder 23 / 3)
    - Knowles Dam hearing (related material), 1962 (Box-folder 23 / 4)
    - Knowles Dam hearing (testimony, statements, and resolutions in support of dam), 1963 (Box-folder 23 / 5)
    - Knowles Dam hearing (related material), 1963 (Box-folder 23 / 6)
    - Knowles Dam hearing (includes testimony of Frances D. Logan, Albert W. Stone, Gus Norwood, Leonard Kenfield, Jeanne Beaty, S.R. Logan, Lumber and Sawmill Workers Union), 1963 (Box-folder 24 / 1-2)
    - Knowles Dam hearing (related material), 1963-1964 (Box-folder 24 / 3)
    - In the Matter of Montana Power Company Project #5 (re Kerr Dam evaluation), 1965 (Box-folder 24 / 4)
    - In the Matter of Montana Power Company and Confederated Salish and Kootenai Tribes Project #2507 (re Kerr Dam and proposed Buffalo Rapids dams), 1965 (Box-folder 24 / 5)
    - Clark Fork and Flathead River water resources study hearings, 1966 (Box-folder 24 / 6)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 24 / 7)
  - Miscellany
    - Miscellaneous (includes statements, brochures, etc.), undated (Box-folder 24 / 8)
  - Transfers
    - Lists of photographs and printed material transferred to Photo Archives and Library respectively (Box-folder 24 / 9-10)